Kong Pui Yee Bonnie

Telephone: 6285 8787

Address: Flat M, 32/F Block 1, Fu Ning Garden,

25 Po Ning Road, Tseung Kwan O, NT

E-Mail: bonyeeyee@hotmail.com

SUMMARY

Responsible and competitive Fund Accounting Assistant Manager in ADM Capital, an Investment manager focusing on Asset Management and in charge of large-scale fund accounting, valuation and administrative work for both Private Equity and Hedge Funds. Being a strong coordinator and team player with positive, cooperative and independent characters, evidenced by 9 years' audit related and fund accounting experiences.

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

Jun 2011- Present Certified Public Accountant, Hong Kong Institute of Certified Public Accountants

EDUCATION

Jun 2008 – Aug 2008	City University of Hong Kong
	Postgraduate Certificate in Professional Accounting
Sep 2005 – May 2008	Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (HKUST)
	Bachelor of Business Administration in Management of Organizations and Marketing-
	Second Class Honor
Sept 1998 - Mar 2005	Belilios Public School
	HKAL (1A 1B 1C 2D)

HKCEE (3A 3B 2C)

Mrs Choi Chui Luk Memorial Scholarship, Outstanding Student Award

AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS

Jun 2011	Member, HKICPA
Jun 2008	Common Recruitment Examination, HKSAR Government: Pass in Aptitude Test
Apr 2008	State Putonghua Proficiency Test, HKUST: Grade Three
Aug 2007	International English Language Testing System (IELTS): 7.5 out of 9
Jul 2005	Office of the Commissioner of Insurance: Pass with Insurance Intermediaries Qualifying
	Examination Paper 1 and 3
Dec 2004	London Chamber of Commerce and Industry Examinations Board : Pass in Level 3
Dec 2002	London Chamber of Commerce and Industry Examinations Board: Pass with Distinction
	in Level 1

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Jun 2011- Present

Fund Accounting, Assistant Manager, ADM Capital

- To prepare timely and accurate Net Asset Values for Private Equity Funds and Hedge Funds, equipped with product knowledge of various security types and derivatives
- To prepare the IRR data, financial statements and fund portfolio reports
- To reconcile the cash and handle all the middle office work which support the front and back office teams, being strong supporter in liaising and assisting the Investor Relationship and Risk Management teams.
- To execute fund administrative work, such as preparing capital call and distribution notices, payment instructions, price input, forward exchange contracts and trade settlements
- To assist and tackle issues for Annual audit and cooperate with auditors

Kong Pui Yee Bonnie Telephone: 6285 8787 **Address:** Flat M, 32/F Block 1, Fu Ning Garden, **E-Mail:** bonyeeyee@hotmail.com

75 Do Ning Dood, Tooma Vivon O. NT

25 Po Ning Road, Tseung Kwan O, NT

 To keep the full set accounting for SPVs and tax filing and annual review of Beijing Office and Wuhan SPVs

Apr 2010- Jun 2011

• To have strong experience in dealing with funds' Custodian Bank and Administrators

Fund Accountant, The Hong Kong and Shanghai Banking Corporation Limited

- To provide fund accounting and valuation services for Hedge Fund and Private Equity Investment
- To handle daily fund administrative and operational work and act as a good communicator on behalf of clients with investors, auditors and fund houses
- To calculate NAV and prepare weekly, monthly reports and financial statements

Sep 2008- Mar 2010

Audit Associate, Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu

- To provide statutory auditing services for engagement clients,
- To prepare auditor reports and perform analytical procedures on account balances and classes of transactions
- To be assigned in large-scale audit engagements such as China Resources
 Microelectronics, Cheung Kong Infrastructure etc.
- To complete the small engagements independently

Jan - Jan 2008 Student Helper, Admissions, Registration and Records Office of HKUST

(Summer Job) • To handle documents and clerical work

• To file documentation and deal with MS Chinese word processing

Jun - Jul 2007 Development Assistant, **Hitachi Beijing Tech Information System Co. Ltd**

(Summer Job) • To accomplish a Design Project with the specialized computer program in Beijing

To organize data list and analyze the data reports

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

May 2006 - May 2007 Executive Committee, Promotion Secretary, Drama Team member, Drama Society, HKUSTSU

- To design promotion products and design the promotion strategy for all activities
- Person in charge of Drama Orientation Camp and Annual Performance 2007
- Producer of Annual Performance 2007

Sep 2005 - Jun 2006

Sub Committee and membership, HKUST

- Sub Committee member of Drama Society, Accounting Society, Marketing Society, and Student Social Service Society
- Member of House IV floor committee and HKUST Handball Team

Sep 2003 - Aug 2005

School Perfect, Vice-chairperson of Photography Club, Treasurer of Chinese Club and Class

Committee, Belilios Public School

SKILLS AND INTERESTS

Language English (Fluent), Cantonese (Native), Mandarin (Fluent)

Computer Quickbook, Advent Geneva, EquiTrak, MS Office applications, SAP, SPSS

Interests and others Travelling, drama production, making new friends, drawing

EXPECTED SALARY HKD48,000 (Current yearly package: US72,846 with monthly salary HKD40,000)

AVAILABILITY ASAP